I'm here.
I'm ready.
I'm ready to play!
Oh, man.
I was speed eating just now.
I wasn't really feeling like playing the last couple days.
And then today, I wasn't feeling like it either.
But then like half an hour ago, I was like, fuck!
I'm really feeling it.
And I couldn't wait until three o'clock, so here I am.
You're speed shitting now.
I don't understand people that can do that.
That's impressive to me.
I take forever when I'm on the toilet.
I just can't not sit on my phone or whatever.
It's a bad habit.
Then I stand up and my left leg is like sleeping.
That's when you know you've been sitting for too long.
It's bad.
Yeah, maybe I do need more fiber.
Oh, man.
Man, the allergies have been killing me.
I don't know how it is with you guys, but these months right now, it's bad.
The last couple days was hell.
Oh, my God.
I'm probably going to be sneezing quite a bit today, but I'm going to try and ninja-click the mute button so you don't get to experience that, of course.
It's also raining here.
Artabingo boy.
Nice name.
It doesn't work for me.
Like, it doesn't matter.
Rainy, sunny.
The allergies are killing me.
It doesn't even matter, unfortunately.
Just living a bubble?
You know what?
I thought about it, man.
I always thought and future would be so cool if you could have this sort of membrane around your body.
That completely isolates you from whatever, you know, like everything is just clean, filtered, clean room air inside that membrane.
I would love that.
Maybe even a wall?
A wall doesn't work.
At least not the walls I'm used to.
I could wear an allergy mask, but that sounds annoying.
I want the future to have something where I don't even notice that the membrane is there, you know?
Feel free.
Exactly.
A pressurized gaming room.
It's actually not a bad idea.
Like, a mini clean room, you know, set up.
Where's Bubble Boy from, anyway?
I know there's a thing with the Bubble Boy.
Is that a movie or something?
Like, he walks around in a bubble, right?
Like, actually, like a spherical bubble.
I don't think there's asbestos, that's not the problem.
It's only during summer months.
It's birch, it's grass, it's all these other weird designations.
I think right now grass is peaking.
At least in the part of the world where I live.
Okay, guys, we're gonna start playing this game.
Because I'm a little too excited.
We unlocked new characters last time.
Hold on.
Oh god, I'm not a good producer!
There we go.
Could have been more smooth, but you know, it is what it is.
Okay, let's see here.
Also, I gotta clean my glasses.
One second, my glasses...
When I saw the screen, like the Brights Isaac screen, I noticed how dirty my glasses are.
That needs to be fixed.
There we go.
Nice and clean.
Okay.
What did I unlock?
I unlocked something new last time.
Not Bethany, not Eulith.
This guy, Samson.
Yeah, Samson.
Undying rage and berserk.
No idea what that means.
Let's check it out.
Oh wait, three hearts, two boots and one knife.
Okay.
Nothing?
Three red hearts?
3.5 damage?
Fuck it, I'm going in here.
I'm feeling it.
Oh, these guys have a lot of HP.
Oh.
Okay, not too bad.
You don't want to become too small, though.
Otherwise, you can't see your character.
There's a sweet spot there, for sure.
Whoa.
I wonder what this guy's gimmick is.
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
No, I don't know.
I don't know what the gimmick is.
I thought I saw something on the left side of the screen, but I was like, no, that angel symbol has always been there.
Really?
Nothing?
Not even a single?
Okay, there we go.
Thank you.
I was about to raise a... or throw a temper tantrum.
Oh!
Wait, wait, wait.
Do we want this?
I think we do.
Of course we want this.
What am I talking about?
Always want this.
Yeah, so we're gonna need... Oh, shit.
More damage.
Wait, what's happening?
Okay, I guess that's the gimmick.
I don't understand the gimmick.
No clue what's happening.
Okay.
I ain't got money, bro.
Oh, man.
This buffer is looking tasty.
I think I'll save for that.
I do like my buffers.
So whatever just happened, it looked like I went into some sort of melee mode, and I could not control my Ludovico.
So I think I may have already fucked myself on this character.
But this is all very premature.
I could be totally wrong.
This is my read on it.
Okay, okay, okay.
Oh!
Oh, okay.
I see.
So when that happens, you only have a certain amount of time for it.
And when you hit enemies with it, you get more time.
I don't know what's triggering it, though.
Like, why is it activating?
Maybe it's on a timer.
Or maybe it's after I kill X amount of enemies.
How did I get hit by that?
You saw that?
Oh, wait.
We're doing it.
Oh, go, go, go.
I'm using the... we're slicing.
It's sliced, nerd.
Oh, it didn't work.
Ran out.
Too bad.
I mean, Ludovico is good, man.
I'm liking the Ludo.
Oh, here we go.
Shit.
Dude, I don't know if I like that.
No!
Worst item in the game.
Maybe not the worst, but it's definitely up there.
I can't buy my buffer.
I can't even buy HP.
I'm fucked.
This is bad.
Shit.
This is a rough start.
Okay, we got demon mode.
Come on, man.
I'm just gonna follow him.
Oh!
Oh, fuck.
I almost get like a jump scare when that happens.
Mr. Boom.
Oh, okay.
I mean, that's not bad.
I actually kind of like that.
So, wait.
Is that the one where I spawn and then throw?
Or is it spawning where I press the button?
Let me try certain things.
Okay, nice.
Hey, I need that.
Nice.
I don't want to enter here yet.
I'm gonna try this here.
Yeah, okay.
So, it is just spawning where I'm standing.
Good amount of damage, I guess.
Let's go this way.
Are we gonna turn into the whatever?
Nope.
We're not turning into the whatever yet.
Oh, wait a minute.
We're turning red.
Are we turning red with time?
Or is it the amount of kills?
Maybe it's the amount of kills.
Okay, so this one.
I really want that coin.
Let's see what this is.
Spider baby.
Sure.
Why not?
We gotta find the boss immediately, though, so we don't lose the demon chance.
Just stay at range here.
The lovers, nice.
I should take care of these.
Okay.
I could bomb those.
No, I'm gonna save it for a boss.
Oh, no.
Oh, shit.
Where's my thing?
Oh, God.
I can't focus my eyes on two things.
Oh, my God.
That was crazy.
Here we go.
Wish me luck.
Duke of Flies.
I'm gonna kill these.
I'm gonna turn into the guy now.
Here we go.
That's for you.
Not bad, eh?
Didn't even need a buffer, baby.
Let's see.
Squeeze.
Okay, so here's the question.
Do we take a deal?
Or do we go nuts and go angel mode?
Guys, I think I'm going angel.
I'm an angel fan nowadays.
I've changed.
I have.
It's the truth.
Let's go this way now.
I don't know how much I like the melee attack.
Oh, no.
How did I not get hit?
The Empress is actually pretty good as well.
Oh, I shouldn't have picked up those two buffers.
That was a mistake.
I see that now.
Because I could have gone into the curse room and used the lovers to get the health back and then taken the buffer, you know?
But whatever.
Let's do this.
Wonderful.
Not wonderful.
That's bad.
Sup, dude?
Oh, we turned into a madman.
Ace of clubs.
Transforms all pickups, chests, trinkets and enemies into bombs.
That doesn't sound super good.
Ah, but wait, it's only in the room you're in.
It's not like forever.
I thought this was like a permanent thing for the rest of the run.
I don't know why I assumed that.
Like, every time I saw this card, I thought that's what that did.
But I guess I can take it.
That's fine.
I mean, if I need some bombs, right?
Then it's actually pretty good.
Now, check it out.
This is a secret.
Maybe.
There's a battery back here I can take.
Before we do, let me check the walls.
Okay, looking good.
What about the... Ah, I can't go in there again, but that was okay.
I think it was fine.
Right here.
Beautiful!
And... Oh, nice!
No!
Like, the last thing I wanted, but okay.
Damn.
I can definitely get this if I'm smart about it.
No, I can just do this.
Nice.
12 coins.
Perhaps we go to shop.
I think I'll take the blue one.
Yep.
That's good.
I could use a... Oh, man.
I could have turned that one.
Wait, is it also money it turns into bombs?
All pickups, chests, trinkets, and enemies!
Oh, wait a sec now!
Enemies, too!
Oh, okay.
This one is better than I thought.
I like it.
The question is, is it going to be turned into the troll bombs or the normal ones that I can pick up?
We are done here.
Go!
Third floor.
I feel like my Ludovico technique is kind of fighting against the mechanic of this character.
I'm going to hide over here.
Sick.
I wonder if the buff you get when you go into melee mode is going to persist between rooms.
Like, three rooms or something, you know?
Oh, shit.
Take the bombs out first.
There we go.
Oh, shit!
Okay, here we go, here we go.
Shit.
Oh, yeah, I'm maintaining it.
Look.
Oh, shit.
Let's go.
No, I'm too slow.
Damn, I thought I had more time.
Oh, my God, dude.
Nose goblin.
Oh, that's a good one.
I want that.
I like it.
Ha!
The nose goblin.
Oh, my God, the nose goblin from range.
Oh, shit, here we go.
Yeah, yeah, we still have it.
Man, this doesn't last long, does it?
Doesn't seem that good, man.
Maybe in rooms like this it's pretty good.
Like, the duration on it is just too low.
Uh, 33% chance of Angel.
I like it.
Let's go.
Choop.
I'm going to blow up the smithereens.
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait.
It's when I take damage.
I think.
Oh, wait a sec.
Oh, it is.
Oh, my God.
We can't lose the buffer.
Why do we have it again now?
Oh, okay, maybe it's the amount of damage you do.
Maybe it's not related to kills.
I have no idea.
No, Angel.
Latchkey, okay.
Uh, I could turn that into a bomb.
No, I don't want to.
I'm good.
Okay, interesting.
No idea why we transformed, like, four times during that, but... whatever.
Man, I need the stat that makes my thing move faster across the screen.
Shot speed, I guess.
Because this is taking forever to move this Ludovico around.
Okay, I'll take those.
Kind of want to go in there.
Let's wait.
I could bomb that.
Not sure of worth.
Imagine having flying in this room.
That would
be nice.
These guys, actually.
Slowly but surely.
Sick.
And we got treasure.
Come on, please be good.
Okay, not bad.
I like it.
And more money.
Thirteen now.
There's also a shop we haven't visited yet.
Oh, there we go.
Wait, oh, wait, I can charge something.
Oh, I can.
Oh, I see.
I can throw it.
Oh, my God.
Okay, well, that's going to change things.
Very nice.
I'm feeling a secret right here, but we only have one bomb, so let me just...
Okay, looking good.
Nope, that's not it.
Maybe up here.
This is looking good.
Let's check the right side.
Nope.
Okay, so it's not there either.
It could be the one actually down here.
Looks like a bunch of rooms surrounding a tiny square to the left here.
Okay, that's good.
That's good.
Yeah, that actually looks pretty good.
The fact that that is even connected there... Yeah, this is definitely it.
Oh, never mind.
Shit.
Then I have no idea.
I'm going to fight.
Getting more bombs is good.
Am
I going to unlock the fucking special move soon?
Wake up.
Okay, got energy back now.
Oh, here we go.
Let me try this.
Like a boomerang or... Dude, it lasts like three seconds.
Fucking useless.
You got to do something special with that to maintain it.
I'm going in here.
Fuck!
Terrible room.
Okay, well, time for the shop and then we leave.
Come
on, one more coin.
Uno, mas.
Please.
Okay, you know what?
I make my own luck.
Fuck you.
I blow it up then.
I don't give a shit.
We're taking this.
Mom's box.
What was that one?
Sponsor Trinket.
Lost Cork?
I'm not feeling it, man.
Although the box is nice.
Maybe I keep that instead of the bomb.
It's not too bad.
Also, we have ten coins left.
Can we somehow scrounge up five more?
Perhaps.
Nah, I'm leaving.
Getting out of here.
Let's go.
67% Angel.
I could use a bomb here, but let's not.
Oh, crap.
Ooh, that was scary.
Okay, I'm not gonna fall for this one.
Okay, nice.
Laos!
Chance of spawning two blue spiders every time Isaac is in a room with enemies?
Spawns a blue spider on room clear?
No.
I mean, that's a trinket, right?
Yeah, it is.
So, apparently, this is better now because of the box, right?
Yeah, 20% chance to fire a booger now.
75% chance for the booger to be homing.
Wow.
That's not bad.
An appeal.
Infested.
I mean, we could turn some of this stuff into bombs.
Oh, no!
Don't do that now.
Equality.
Grants a large fire rate increase when collected coins, bombs...
No.
That one seems so incredibly hard to utilize.
I mean, it depends.
Like, how big of a fire rate are we talking?
Maybe it is good.
Ah, but the booger, though.
Please.
Kill him!
Nice.
Another one of these.
Oh, no, I have no keys.
I'm actually in trouble.
Kill him!
Oh, my goodness.
Okay.
Can't get in there, either.
Let's make a new trinket.
Demon's tail.
80% of drop hearts are replaced with keys.
I mean, I kind of need that right now.
Blue and purple fires drop black.
I mean, that's... Honestly, the demon's tail is pretty damn good.
I may just go with that.
Booger, though, is kind of a big deal in my DPS right now.
Ah, damn.
Okay,
that's a key.
But we can't get in there.
I'm playing this so safe.
Okay.
Damn it.
Ah, yes.
It's gonna take a couple, but that's okay.
We're gonna destroy all these mushrooms.
Okay, we got the key.
Good shit.
We go back, we open the treasure room.
This is the most important thing right now.
Blood of the martyr.
More damage is always welcome.
We like it.
I wonder if that affects my effect, you know, when I go melee.
Probably does.
I still need a key for the shop.
Surely we can find that.
Oh, no.
Don't.
Oh, scary.
Oh,
here we go.
I haven't turned into a thingy.
Dude, it's useless, man.
It doesn't do any damage.
If I go into melee, at least give me like a huge boost to damage, you know?
Okay, let's see what we get.
Broken Onk.
Chance to revive.
Oh, okay.
Maybe I'll change it.
We'll see.
Dude, my damage is pretty good.
Also, my tier is very large.
Hopefully we can make it larger.
Imagine Brimstone.
Gods.
Where's the boss at?
I mean, yeah.
Damn, it's fucked right in front of the boss, man.
I lose all my Destiny points, I was about to say.
Angel points.
Wait, no, we're fine.
How come we're fine?
Is it because we had the green heart instead?
Oh, shit.
That may actually be the reason.
I like it.
Dark one.
Oh, no, we're this now.
Yoy, yoy, yoy.
Okay, oh, he's doing it again.
What are you doing?
Oh, nice.
A screw?
Man, no, Angel, even with 67% chance.
Moms lock it.
Heal for one red heart, whenever Isaac unlocks something.
Hmm.
Ah, nah, I like my tail.
I like being a demon.
This is demon.
This is not gonna work.
I wanna go in here, actually.
Well, let's pick up a heart first.
The strategy is sound.
We can also go to the shop now.
Actually, let's go there first, in case there's something I can use.
Ooh, that 15 one, I want that.
Nice.
Let's see.
Oh, I should have gone here first.
Shit.
I mean, the screw was good, I guess.
Not too bad.
Okay, thanks.
Good item.
Now for the curse.
What about fight room?
Ooh, I'm actually gonna do this.
Un-fucking-real.
That actually just pissed me off, man.
I got a little upsetting spaghetti, I'm not gonna lie.
Order of operations.
You know, I don't give a shit.
We're going in.
I'm very excited.
Dammit.
Wait, how come I didn't pick up that heart?
Why is it still there?
No, there were two hearts.
Yeah.
There we go.
There's also a half-on-red heart down here we can grab.
No buffer, unfortunately.
Sometimes you gotta gamble.
I think maybe secret's here.
Could it be right here?
I don't know, I can't tell.
No, it cannot.
Dude, secrets have not been obvious to me in this run at all.
I'm having trouble with it.
Let's go.
Okay, a hundred percent angel now, but we're probably gonna take damage, so rip.
Okay.
I'm scared of spiky chests.
So... okay.
We still are excited.
Yeah, let's do it.
Yeah, that's a buffer.
Nevermind, buffer gone.
Love it.
You could not run that.
That was impossible.
I'm too slow.
You need more speed.
Now I'll just get in here.
Oh, sick!
Rich.
Let me see here, additional bomb.
I don't think I want that right now.
You can have some bombs.
Not too many.
Okay, I mean, take me to 15.
Scatter bombs.
Yeah, I like it.
Now, do I go in there?
I don't think I do.
Yes, I do.
Oh, no.
Oh, soul hearts, baby!
Oh, wait, that's not soul hearts.
This is the one.
Buffer, achieve.
We got the clubs and... you know what?
No, keep it.
Keep it for now.
We got to find a shop.
I'm going to get in here.
Now that I have extra bombs.
Oh, yeah!
The buffer, we may be okay here.
Oh, we turned into a madman.
Dude, speed run.
Ah, man, I was going to try and maintain it.
Oh, shit, here we go.
Okay, not bad.
Okay, kind of bad.
Lucky rock.
Rocks and other obstacles have a chance to drop two pennies.
Let's keep that in mind in case we find something that allows us to break rocks.
Golden horseshoe.
Chance for the... Oh, I like that one.
Let's keep that until we find the treasure room at least.
That's not bad.
Here it is.
Yeah, okay.
I mean, it can't be bad, right?
It's going to make this weird, I think.
Oh, oh.
Okay.
Keep going.
Speed.
Yes.
Oh, my God, you got to... Dude, if you want to keep that up, you got to go fast.
No!
Open your mouth!
Nice!
I like that one.
Hookworm.
Ah, no thanks.
I'm good.
I wish I knew how to trigger the melee effect on command.
Where's the boss at?
Oh, I should change my trinket, actually.
Oh, here we go, here we go.
Wait, I'm bouncing around my own little... Yo, my Ludo Vico can get bounced by my slice.
That's incredible.
Wow.
Blow it.
Nice.
Please spawn more.
Spawn more bombs.
Oh, here we go, here we go.
Oh, shit.
Oh, right.
Oh, my God.
Good.
Crackjacks or... dog food, obviously crackjacks.
Paperclip, no thanks.
Let's see the angel offerings.
Holy water!
I have started to really like that one.
It's a goodie.
Oh, we have turned into a thingy.
Wait, okay, disappeared again.
Shit!
Dude, I'm so confused!
Oh, I can hit enemy attacks back as well?
Okay, that's pretty good.
It's not just my own.
That is pretty damn good.
Monkey paw.
This one is a pretty good survival item, actually.
I don't mind that, but I think I'd rather have the demon tail.
Poop explodes when destroyed, actually.
No, it's a trinket.
Too many damn trinkets.
We're not going yet.
There are things to be done.
Where's that trinket at?
It's all the way up there, I think.
Wait, what the frick?
Okay, I feel like it right here.
Damn!
Why did I just guess?
I could go in there and grab that battery.
This guy wants hearts.
It's tempting.
Still haven't found a shop either, by the way.
Wait, where the hell is my trinket?
Is it that one?
Ah, there it is.
I actually forgot what it does.
Hearts are now keys, and all the heart drops become black hearts.
That's pretty damn good.
Let's find the shop.
Not here.
Okay, I'm excited and smaller.
You know what?
Why not?
Fence zoom.
This one's gonna shoot me.
Or a Boros worm.
Nah, I'm good.
Whoa, mystery gift!
Is the angel room open, though, is the question.
Oh, what's that?
Smelter.
Consumes the currently held trinket and grants its effect as a... Wait a sec, now.
Hold on.
This could actually be crazy, guys.
Slightly increases the chance of finding trinkets as room clear rewards.
Dude, we have so many trinkets on the map.
Look at that.
We have batteries on the map as well.
This could be it.
I'm buying it.
Okay, so watch it.
Wait, is it the full effect?
Grants its effect as a permanent.
Damn!
Okay, so now I just have it.
Let's go get a battery.
There's actually a battery in here.
Maybe I can... There's also a re-roll thing.
Hold on now.
This is getting exciting.
Let's do this.
Okay, so which one do we want?
Let me see.
I don't know about that one.
That's a little bit... Wait, how does that even work with my... Ludovico?
Oh, that's... Oh, that's horrible.
That's absolutely terrible.
There's no way I want that.
Only a madman would take it.
Now we have a trinket here.
This one is also pretty good.
Let's keep an eye around here.
This one?
More bombs?
That's not bad, man.
So wait, do we have more?
There's also a trinket in the boss room.
Wait, wait, wait.
I need to really think about this.
This is a big moment here.
I'm going to go back to the boss room.
I don't remember what I had.
Oh, paperclip.
Lock chest can be opened without using... It's not a bad idea, I guess.
But I'm kind of hoping for some combat trinkets, right?
Oh, dude, we can even spawn a new one with the box.
Wait, there's so many options here.
There are so many options here.
But we need energy on that and we don't have it.
This is the problem.
I think I want this one.
Smelled it down.
And then we go grab... Oh, wait, wait, let me think.
I could go in there, maybe.
Give some hearts.
Also, what about secret?
Do we blow this up?
Ah, but that's the last bomb we have.
Ooh, this is a rough one.
Speeds up everything.
How does this feel?
Let me see how this feels.
Oh my god, it's terrible!
Ow!
That's even worse than what we had before.
Terrible, terrible.
No thanks.
I think the last trinket I'm gonna smelt is gonna be one of these two up here.
This one was the... Yeah, this one is pretty good, I guess.
Let's go smelt that one.
I like it.
Gonna grab the battery from in here.
Oh, shit.
That was an accident.
Smelt!
And then we have another trinket we can grab.
The question is, which one do I take?
There's also one in here.
Oh, shit, I forgot about this one.
I think I'll take this one with me.
Yeah.
By the way, the tier stat is useless for me.
It doesn't do anything.
Actually, maybe it does.
Maybe it increases the tick rate at which my thing ticks for damage.
Either that or shot speed.
No, shot speed would be the speed at which I can move it around, I guess.
Man, I've just been walking around back and forth too much here.
I need to leave.
I could re-roll this.
No, I can't.
I have no bombs.
Shit.
I'm gonna keep the smelter.
Yeah.
We're gonna run with this.
I can turn things into bombs.
What?
Nothing got... What?
What do you mean, nothing got turned into bombs?
At least something in here should have turned into... Okay, whatever, dude.
Unbelievable.
Like, if those are not pickups, then my name isn't Brad, you know?
I feel cheated.
All right, let's go.
Moving on.
Okay, it's time for mom.
21% angel.
What happened there?
Oh, got taken.
Go, go, go.
You can't make it.
Holy shit.
Where's my thingy?
Oh, I can't see it.
Move it away.
Yo, the fact that I can move bombs with my... I never thought about that, but that's something I can do.
Here we go.
No!
There goes my angel.
It was nice knowing you.
Oh, crap.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's not going well.
You know what, actually, the holy water is not very good with Ludovico.
The synergy isn't there.
Chances spawn a red heart when damaged.
Taking damage will make Isaac... Wait, hold on.
Taking damage will make Isaac gush.
Blood tears.
Every 20 seconds while bleeding lose half a red heart.
But how do I stop bleeding, though?
It sounds bad.
It sounds like I'm gonna keep taking damage.
Oh, wait, I shouldn't have done that.
Hold on.
Destroy this.
Invested.
Poke go.
Battery.
Battery is important, maybe.
This thing's gonna spawn trinkets, guys.
This may actually be good.
I don't want anything from the shop.
Oh!
We're gonna absorb that one.
Absorbation.
No!
Here we go.
You have been absorbed.
I'm gonna take this back.
I'm gonna keep donating.
The Hierophant.
Love that one.
More trinkets, come on.
Please.
Shit.
Well, we had to give it a shot.
Let's play it safe.
I'm just gonna hide back here.
Oh, here we go.
Honestly, dude, I don't like the mechanic on this character.
We're not gonna go inside yet.
I guess the plan is to go and kill, let me think.
What do we even wanna do?
I'm just sort of messing around right now.
I could buy the battery and get this trinket absorbed, but not yet.
Nice!
That's a good item.
And AWAS as well.
Oh, I love AWAS.
My favorite.
I'll take it.
The world, I like that too.
Question is, how do I... Ah, I see.
Oh, how life is so much easier when you can fly, huh?
One secret room.
I wonder why only one.
Okay, here we go.
I shouldn't have done that.
That was a mistake.
Orphan socks.
Speed and soul hearts.
Allows walking on ground.
Shouldn't have absorbed the other one.
Does not prevent damage from curse room doors or sacrifice spikes.
Oh, you're talking about the step room.
Sacrifice room.
I'm gonna take these.
We have a plenty buffer right now and it's nice.
I'm gonna go west.
Don't hit me.
What happened?
Wait, I can destroy these?
Did you see that?
That's freaking noose.
What?
I had no idea you'd do that.
That's crazy.
Mind blown.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Open up your mouth.
I mean, we're getting rich again, so a shop would be kind of sweet.
We can smelt now?
I'm gonna do it.
Why not?
May as well do it, right?
Kind of wanna destroy rocks now?
That's how we get money.
Not that I need any right now.
Oh crap.
Yeah, there's no way I could have avoided that.
Lucky penny.
I guess I'll go in the curse room.
Yeah, let's do it.
I cannot see my thing I shoot with.
Oh, because I'm melee mode.
We also have Awas.
Question is, where is it good?
This one, this one.
Hell yeah.
Bob's Burgers?
No, it's boom.
Boom.
That's so boring.
The most boring item in the game.
Ew.
Why is my tear so weird?
Oh, it was a random effect.
Okay.
It was moving in unpredictable patterns.
Let's get out of here.
There's nothing else we want to do, right?
No more trinkets to absorb?
Actually, hold on.
Donate a bunch of money here.
And what was in here?
Dude, I'm going to buy this.
No reason not to.
Now we donate.
Hoping for another trinket.
Strength.
Okay, that's not bad, actually.
Just one more for the road.
Ooh, we could do that and then go to home with it.
If we want to.
Actually, let's do that.
I've never tried that with a dark character.
I'm going to bomb this, by the way.
Nice.
Bomb this, too.
I have so many bombs.
Grab the pool.
Wait, wait, wait.
Yes, yeah, yeah.
Go.
This is good.
We are indeed aligned.
Mom!
Wait, what?
How did these coins spawn?
Oh, we're transformed.
This is weird.
Oh, God.
Mom!
Dude, the noodle vehicle is so confusing when you have the melee.
Jesus Christ.
Okay, take this.
Don't fall down.
No angel, unfortunately.
But it's fine.
I'll take that.
Fool me.
Once, twice on you, and so forth and so on.
Okay.
I think we're done here, right?
Let me think.
Let's take a fight room is open, actually.
No, it's not.
Other than that, we have a card.
Actually, there's a card.
Yeah, grab the card.
And I think we're done now.
Thank you.
I need more trinkets.
I have become addicted to trinkets.
Jump down the hole.
There's no shop down here.
So it's good that we don't have any money.
Wait, this is awkward.
Nice.
That's awesome.
He has been deactivated.
Oh, no.
All right, the DPS is good.
When you finally are transformed.
Oh, my God, more.
Don't mind if I do.
Where's my character?
Oh, there it is.
Look how massive that is.
Dude, I need a trinket so I can smelt.
So weird to have like, like a little airplane, you know, when you have the nail effect.
Shit.
What the hell is... Wow, man.
That seems impossible to dodge.
More black hearts.
I like it.
And of course, we get coins because we have the trinket absorbed.
That gives me coins when I destroy rocks.
How am I gonna... Wait, can I maybe kill this thing?
Let's try.
Let's just wait a bit and see what happens.
Sometimes a random effect.
No.
I think I may be safe.
But how am I gonna do this without taking damage?
We can make this guy push the buttons.
Oh, my God.
Okay, not bad.
Is that a trinket?
Car battery.
Doubles the effects of most... Wait, how does that work?
Do I just get two charges on my...
All right, not that I can afford it anyway, but you know.
Maybe I'll be back.
Also, there is a shop here, apparently.
I thought that wasn't...
Not bad.
Okay, I think I'm ready.
No, I'm not.
This is gonna lead me to the next area immediately.
There's no boss there.
We pick up the piece of paper and then we go, right?
Where's my... I can't see my projectile.
There it is.
Dude, my build is fucked.
I don't like Ludovico.
I think I only like it on Azazel.
This is absolute trash.
I'd rather just shoot normally.
Replaces tears with a charge shot.
Well, is that it?
What?
I don't know what's happening.
I have no idea what's happening right now.
It doesn't feel like anything changed.
Okay, what about Fight Club?
Closed.
You know what?
I'm gonna destroy these.
Nothing.
We're missing something up here.
We're not gonna get far with this build, by the way.
Oh, no.
What's that?
Curse of the Tower?
That one could maybe... No, no.
Last time it was a disaster.
Bad idea.
I think we're done here.
Let's go.
Let's hope for some more trinkets.
Not bad.
I want that.
Harder to hit, right?
Harder to see as well, though?
Here?
Gym, gym, gym, gym, gym.
Solid.
I may actually change out my trinkets or my active as soon as I get the chance.
It's starting to become useless.
Dead weight.
Yeah, why not?
No, no!
I didn't mean to blow them up.
Mistakes were made.
Oh, right.
This thing.
Let me actually understand this.
So, when is this good?
Chances brought a Red Heart and damage.
Taking damage will make Isaac gush blood tears.
And every 20 seconds while bleeding, you lose half a Red Heart.
Running out of Red Hearts or healing Red Hearts will stop.
Okay.
Why is this good?
Because of the 20... it doesn't even seem good?
Okay, we'll make him gush blood tears.
Maybe that's good.
I'm gonna try it, man.
Fuck it.
I need to see how this works in action.
This run is already fucked, I guess.
Time to experiment.
What the hell?
What just happened?
Dude, I cannot see my character.
It's over.
Oh, oh!
There was a thingy in there!
Uh, what was the other one I had?
Strength?
Uh, no.
I'm using this.
Not yet.
We got worms!
Dude, my tear is moving in a weird way right now.
Oh my god, really?
Guys, it's over.
It has never been more over.
Never has it been more over.
Okay, we got a Black Heart, that's something.
Oh, wait, I'm bleeding.
Yeah, this is bad.
This item is exactly as bad as I thought it was gonna be.
I hate it.
Okay, we'll stop bleeding at least.
There's also a half a Red Heart up here.
But who knows, maybe the DPS from it will be enough to clutch.
I doubt, though.
Another one?
I don't understand, like, how that works.
Oh my god.
Ah!
I didn't mean to leave.
It just happened.
Oh, okay, here we go.
I can't see nothing.
This ability on my projectile is, like, it's the hardest game element to see in the game right now.
Okay, that's a trinket, we use it.
Alright, there's also a Black Heart, it seems.
Oh my, stop!
I hate the transformation.
I wish it wouldn't transform me.
Ooh, I can't get that.
Yes, I can.
That's something.
Ooh, what do we have here?
Oh, that could be really good.
Speed even more size down.
Yikes.
I think we crossed the threshold.
It's actually not good for me anymore to get size down.
Wait a minute.
Hold on.
I have an idea.
Check it out.
Let me just double check here.
No, where's the other key?
Was that last floor?
It may have been, actually.
No, it's here.
Okay, okay, so check it out.
We're gonna use one here.
Ooh.
Nice.
Oh, shit.
Okay.
This guy's not gonna spawn trinkets though.
What happened?
Oh, okay.
Honestly, bombs are important.
Portable.
Hey, okay, nice.
I'm so tiny.
Okay,
that was it.
Gambling is done.
Interesting.
And now we grab the other key and save it.
Yeah.
Now, where did I ascend?
Here.
Not bad.
We need some more HP though.
This is important.
You are insane.
You are taking this to your heart.
Did you hear how you sound?
Shut up, Mom.
Stop.
Look how much HP this guy has.
You know what?
Check it out.
I'm gonna leave this heart here.
In case I start bleeding, I'm gonna come back for it.
Huh?
Advanced strategies.
I'm gonna blow that up.
I need pills, man.
Pills.
Okay, that's my exits.
Oh, we're still in this mode.
Ace of space.
Chance of finding a card as a room clear reward.
Is that a trinket?
Nice.
Consumed.
Keep him coming.
Dude, I really like smelter.
The idea behind it is awesome.
Not bad.
This guy's gonna take forever to die.
Dude, we are not gonna be able to kill the bosses.
The Ludovico is going to fuck me.
I won't be able to dodge all the stuff that's happening and also do the Ludovico.
I can tell you right now.
This guy wants coins.
Why not?
Let's not blow him up.
Ah, the cluster bomb's got him.
You know what?
I'm committed.
Make me smaller.
I'm gonna go invisible.
I'm gonna become so tiny that I'm Ant-Man.
I'm too small anyway.
I may as well go all the way, you know?
Dude, this guy can't die.
What the hell?
I can't see my... Wow.
Dude, I don't know where my projectile is.
Oh, it's up here.
Wow.
Stop transforming me, please.
Just... Oh god, it's so confusing.
I don't like this run, man.
This is... I hate this setup.
It's terrible.
I'm just trying to figure out what's happening in every room.
Yeah, okay.
I need to shoot the boob or something.
I need a good active.
I don't know where my thing is there.
I'm bleeding.
Fuck it, just go.
It's looking bad anyway.
Dude, where's my projectile?
Oh my god.
I have no idea what's happening, dude.
I can't play.
Oh, we're in this mode now.
Fucking hell.
This may be the worst character I've ever played in this game.
I'm not even kidding.
I just don't like it at all.
Please die.
I need to see this character without the Ludovico.
Because this right here is absolute trash.
Friendship necklace.
Why not?
Let's consume it.
Let's have them orbit me.
That's probably a good trick.
I beg you.
I just go.
Honestly, we need some insane luck.
We need a D4.
Stat.
Not what I'm looking for.
Sleep.
Okay.
A card?
The sun?
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
Before we take it.
Hold the phone.
Wait, what?
Insane damage upgrades.
Did you see that?
Oh, wait, we lost it again.
Oh, it's the randomized effects.
I thought it was like super special or something.
Mom's key.
That's kind of useless.
The knife is bigger than my body threefold.
Wish me luck, guys.
I am gonna need it.
This is no longer about skill.
This is just... I need luck.
I can't beat it otherwise.
At least we can park the attack thing on the TV and just dodge, right?
That's one thing we can do.
Where's my carrot?
Oh, there it is.
Okay.
Oh, my thing is not parked.
I'm bleeding.
Nice, I'm not bleeding anymore.
This one's gonna be tough now.
Where's my attack?
Oh, there it is.
I'm gonna bomb him.
I missed.
Bomb for you.
Where's my attack?
Oh, shit, I'm melee now.
I'm no longer melee.
Bomb for you.
I hate this attack.
Okay, now focus.
Keep the projectile on him.
Don't transform me.
Don't fucking do it.
Nice.
Okay, good.
Let's see.
No, not this mode.
Dude, my projectile does not move fast enough.
I don't even know where it is.
Oh, there it is.
Dude, what the fuck?
I don't know where my thing is.
Oh, we're meleeing.
Oh, my God.
This feels so bad.
Oh, my God, it's terrible.
Honestly, just keep my projectile on one side of the screen.
No, now he's over there.
Okay.
Oh, I'm melee now.
Shit, where's my thing?
Oh, there it is.
Jesus Christ.
I don't know where my tag is.
Fuck.
The fuck is that?
Dude, I can't see my projectile.
Here's the sun.
Bomb him.
Okay, this is insane.
Dude,
I don't know.
I don't know where my fucking tile is.
There it is.
Oh, this is horrible.
Holy shit.
I don't even know how I'm still alive, honestly.
Keep throwing bombs.
Where's my... Oh, I'm meleeing now?
What is happening?
I have no more bombs.
The bombs are over.
I've got no health.
GG.
I need ultimate flabby birds here.
There's no other way.
Oh, no, I need to move my projectile with the screen, I think.
See about two.
Okay.
Yeah, yeah.
Just melt.
I don't care.
Whoa.
Yeah.
You doing now?
You doing that?
Flabby bird time?
You got it.
Am I doing damage?
Come on.
Flabby birds.
Oh, no.
Where's my attack?
There it is.
Keep it on him.
We're flapping.
Oh, God.
No, I got hit by something.
No!
I'm never playing that character again.
That is fucking terrible.
Absolute terrible.
Let's go with Eden.
What is that hairdo?
Hold on.
Minecrafter?
Okay.
Mercurius.
Most curious.
Most doors remain open in rooms with enemies.
Effect does not apply to boss room doors or ones that require a key to open.
Okay.
I see.
So we can always peace out.
Worst case.
And the TNT stuff.
Using the item again detonates it.
Okay, okay, right.
So I can just be like, nope.
If I want to.
Oh, man, it feels good.
No more Ludovico.
Essays of Ludovico is good.
I just know, like, if they present me with a Ludovico now, like, I'm gonna have to take it.
I don't have the willpower to resist it.
This is the problem.
Number two.
Wait, what?
Firing continuously for three seconds.
Drops a...
I hate it.
I don't even want it.
No, thanks.
Maybe if I really need it, but no.
I'm stuck.
That was so lucky.
Okay, a key for me.
Not bad.
I could blow up some stuff.
Or look for a tinted rock or something.
I could blow this up, actually.
I'm gonna do it.
Six dollars.
The buffer is looking very good, but not until we go to the next floor.
This is the rule.
Oh,
dude, my nose is so itchy.
Ah, just kill it.
Yeah, my nose.
Hold on.
Be right back.
Okay, much better.
Uh, swallow penny.
What was that again?
Sponsor coin each time Isaac takes damage.
Wait a minute, I only have one health.
What the fuck?
That's horrible.
I can't go in here.
Dude, what the hell?
I don't want that.
That's bad.
This could be a secret.
Actually, it is.
What did I say?
More bombs?
Kind of want to go crazy with the pills.
Hopefully get a health up pill.
Trust me.
Here we go.
This is it.
I mean, I can use that.
Man, really?
That's it?
A singular pill.
Crazy.
We also have this one.
No.
I don't want it.
You know what, actually?
No.
Especially not with one HP.
It's going to be a disaster.
We got the Duke of Flies.
I should have had my TNT here, actually.
Would have been nice.
This guy has way too many flies.
Oh, I got a nice opening there.
That was good damage.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's it.
Yes!
Huge.
Very nice.
Oh!
Nose Goblino.
Wait, what the fuck?
Didn't I get this exact same trinket last time and the nose goblin?
I had both of these last time.
What the hell?
Um, I think I'll take it.
Because I don't want to take damage.
Oh, you know what I could do?
Hold on.
We can do Curse Room.
We have an extra heart lying around.
I like it.
AWOS!
Huge!
What's it gonna be?
Uh, oh, this is the, um... fuck me, dude.
What's it called?
Yeah, this is actually a good one.
This is one of the better familiars you can find.
Okay, now we go grab the... heart.
Oh, yeah.
Maybe we keep blowing things up here?
Only spiders.
Also, what did I start with?
Oh, right.
I need to make use of that.
Oh, we also have nine coins.
I wanted to get the buffer, right?
Or I take a health up pill.
No.
I take this.
I would say not a bad first floor.
I've had better.
This guy's gonna be annoying.
Good, the boogers are huge.
Walnut?
Being hit by an explosion has a chance to destroy the trinket and spawn a bunch of shit.
I
mean, how often do I get hit by an explosion, right?
It doesn't really happen.
I do get hit, but explosion specifically, that's... that's a bit too much.
Blowing that up.
Not bad.
Oh, let's get some, uh, some mana here.
Shit.
Those ones.
Good.
Now we go back and blow the shit out of this.
Hourglass.
Oh, this one is actually good, man.
You can make some good stuff happen with this.
Walk into my creep.
No, you want to.
Uh, left first.
There's gonna be a ten coin in here.
I desire it so...
Looks like the boogers are actually going through obstacles to their spectral.
See that?
Damn, no ten coin.
A tenner.
Yeah, walk into my creep.
That's good.
You fucking serious?
I had no idea they could charge.
Caught me off-guard.
Okay, here we go.
Wish me luck.
Oh, Steve... No, that means we're gonna get the Steven item.
Man, I don't like that.
Stay away from me.
I mean, okay, it takes us to two out of three unconjoined.
That is not too bad, actually.
We're not doing demons.
Not with this amount of HP.
I can tell you that.
Okay, let's go back.
Don't even watch that effect just now.
Unbelievable.
Oh, it's Steven shooting.
Right, of course.
That's what that effect is.
48 hour energy is useless for me.
Ooh, that's nice.
That's really good.
I'm gonna donate some money.
The best part about this right now is that we got it early.
So we're gonna get maximum... Can I...
I thought for a second there was a new item in here.
Don't have... Nah, I'll keep the hourglass.
What about the curse room, though?
We have a healing, so... should be okay.
Gopi's head.
Oof.
Nah.
I'm not gonna revert, because I wanna stay on one out of three on Gopi.
Still don't know what it does.
We gotta figure it out, right?
Oh, wait.
I gotta bomb my way in here.
Okay.
Maybe we'll look for a secret, actually.
I predict right down here.
But let's have a look.
Looking good?
Looking real good.
Shit.
Okay, I'm gonna save my last bomb.
Play it safe.
I think it was a good bet, though.
Oh, that was actually a better spot.
Right in the smack dab.
Why didn't I go for that?
That was dumb.
I don't trust, though, so we're just gonna move on.
Cheers.
Curse of darkness, huh?
I'm not afraid of the dark.
Wait, why is this guy not taking damage?
He's red!
He should be taking damage?
What the hell?
Nah, bro, what's happening?
Hello?
I don't understand.
This is not how the game should work.
Okay, whatever.
Let's have a look.
So this room is most definitely just trash, it seems.
We got a bomb out of it?
Okay, that's fine.
I was about to say let's revert it, but we only have two of them left.
Wait, is it actually two for the rest of the run?
Oh, shit.
No, research each floor.
Okay.
Nice.
That's big.
That's really big.
We're gonna try and see if we can get conjoined.
This is one of the objectives of this run right now.
That is one of the better ones.
I hate this room.
Oh, and look for a teleport card.
Because I'm going home, baby.
Bible?
You know what we can do?
Yo, check this out.
This is some next level shit, okay?
Check this out.
We're gonna do this.
Okay, trash?
Trash?
No, thanks.
I'm good on that.
Ha ha ha!
How cool is that?
I was gonna just have a sneak peek at what that pill was gonna do to me.
Uh oh.
Don't go in the corner.
I knew they were gonna turn into skeletons.
That's why I kept my distance.
I felt it in my bones.
Wait.
Okay.
Here we go.
We should have two options.
Lemon mishap or glitter bomb?
I hate them both.
Insane.
Fucking terrible.
But I'll take this, I guess.
I need some of that good shit.
Honestly, uh, Steven is helping a lot there.
The homing tears.
Um, yeah.
Also, what was it?
Something about spawning?
Chance for bombs to drop and pick up or shrinkage?
Wait, how does that make sense?
So wait, the bomb that explodes, you mean?
Has to be.
Very good.
Dude, imagine having backpack?
D6?
And hourglass?
Oh ho!
I wonder if the re-rolls are gonna be in the same order.
You know, if you do that.
Okay, let's go.
Let's create a little office here.
Now step into my office.
Nice.
Keep stepping, come on.
I know you want to.
Lovely.
Oh, there's still one left.
Latchkey again.
Angel!
Huge.
Oh, oh wait, this one.
Right, this one.
Yo, actually, I kind of fuck with it.
Oh, shit.
You know what?
Take me back out.
No!
It doesn't work like that on these rooms.
Well, there we go.
Learned our lesson.
I had no idea.
It's good to learn it, though.
Shit.
Okay, well, it is what it is.
That was very sad.
The beast is loose.
What the?
It was a fly.
I kind of want to reset already with the hourglass.
That's probably pushing it.
Man, this room sucks.
This is a bad room.
Not even a reward for clearing that.
Wait a minute, that's a planetarium!
Saturnus, ring of tears!
A wide halo with seven orbiting tears at the start of each new room.
The halo also has a chance to absorb incoming enemy shots into its orbit, allowing them to damage enemies.
All right.
That sounds pretty good.
Yeah, some of my shots... Yeah, look, some of my shots are green.
Okay, so now I only have three.
But it can absorb more of them.
Oh, my God.
Reset.
Man, this room was actually really annoying.
Okay, nice.
Holy shit, that was a jump.
Good.
They only have a certain range.
If you're outside of that, you're good.
Oh, I'm rich.
Let's see.
We're going to try the pill technique.
What's up with all the energy when I don't need it?
So annoying.
Placebo triggers the effect of the pill.
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
That could actually be kind of sick.
If we find a health uphill, we're going to come back here for sure.
Oh, yeah.
Imagine, though.
But I guess I would have to come back with it without using it and then just hope that it's the right one.
Yeah, otherwise I'd have to find two of them on this floor.
That's crazy.
That ain't happening.
Oh, puberty.
This one, guys.
We get three of those.
We're cooking.
That's one puberty.
When I keep walking around,
we are going to become an adult.
Nice.
Wait, can we just keep doing it?
What if I do three more puberty?
Did we get another health?
Oh, we need to experiment.
Wait.
OK, puberty.
Also, we got to do the boss.
No.
Very good.
Angel.
And we got health.
This is the best day ever.
Rosaries, soul hearts, S copies of the Bible.
That's fine.
Nothing special.
What's up, nerd?
Wait, why do I have like a little ring around me?
Oh, that's where the tears are going when they when they do go.
But they're not going right now.
That hurt me?
Puberty.
I don't think it works, guys.
You can't do puberty again.
You only go through it once in life, which kind of makes sense.
I guess I may just use it.
Yeah.
OK, let's find another cool pill.
We shall become the pill master.
This is the pill run.
Even
got battery here in case we need it late.
Oh, I can't believe I stepped into that.
Also, why am I saying, oh.
Wait, is that because I'm an adult now?
My voice is different.
Is that what's happening?
That's too funny.
Familiar that chases and damages enemies and bombs gain a bigger blast radius.
Give me that one.
What are these shit items in the treasure rooms today?
I don't think any of them.
What I need is flying so I can get these pills.
This is what I really need.
No!
That's like two blue hearts in the toilet.
Flushed.
Yeah, why not?
This will sacrifice everything I have.
Pills!
Mother cracker!
OK, watch this.
You ready?
Give me that.
We're not done.
I need more energy.
Dude, I need energy on this floor.
Maybe I don't, actually.
Show me the good stuff.
Wait, why does my... Hold on a minute.
Why does my active item cost so much mana now?
Oh, variable charge based on the last pill copied.
Oh!
No way!
OK.
Well, hold the phone then.
Then I know what to do.
Ah, but we have no more floors.
What about Fight Club?
It's closed!
Secrets, maybe.
Show me the secrets.
Huh?
Wait, what's...
Oh, right.
That makes sense.
I don't want it.
I'm good.
Basically, here's the plan.
I'm gonna go in here.
No, we need to confirm the existence of a secret route.
No, wait, we have battery somewhere.
There's a battery.
We got battery.
It's a small one.
So check it out.
This is what we're gonna do.
This is so smart, by the way.
You'll see what I mean.
Grab that.
Get out.
We're gonna...
Wait, no.
Oh, shit.
We still need a lot of battery.
It's the last used, not the one equipped.
OK, whatever.
Ah, man!
Fine.
Guess I'll grab it then.
Gracias.
OK, well, we lost some HP there.
That's OK.
Let's gamble a little bit.
Sick.
Just what a man needs.
And I do mean a man, because we're not a boy anymore.
Blow the rest up.
There we go.
This one too.
No, actually, wait.
I'm gonna donate a bit here.
We're gonna make sure we have enough for the next shop.
That should do it.
Not bad.
14 coins, baby.
Go
back up here.
What's that?
Chance for destroyed poops to spawn a pickup.
Nah.
Oh!
Ha!
Hold up now.
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
Let me think.
Very... Oh!
Very good.
Give me that too.
Fucking hell, that's awesome.
And you know what?
Check it out.
I'm gonna use the last pill.
We're gonna grab this now.
Hey!
See you later, nerd!
Now we just need to grab a little bit of HP and not die.
Let's see.
Also, secret maybe over here.
I can see it right here.
I'm so good at the game.
It's astounding.
Good stuff.
And mushroom.
Another pill.
Oh, battery!
I don't need more battery, actually.
Wait, I think I may actually go back and we go full.
I did say full pill run, didn't I?
Dude.
We're not done.
We're going full pill.
Full pill run.
Give me that.
Trust in the process.
I wonder what happens if I... If I get full energy on this and I use it, I'm gonna spawn a bunch of batteries and it's gonna be like crazy.
This is exciting.
I'm ready.
Take me!
This is going to go so hard, guys.
Curse of the blind.
I hate that.
Wait, what does that mean?
Why am I tears like that?
Is that because I'm blind?
I need pills.
That's what he sounds like.
We got shot.
Oh, let's do this one.
No, I don't know what it is.
Metal plated itch.
Wait, what is that one?
Oh, that's good.
That's good.
That's defense right there.
Okay.
There's a question mark.
I really want to get that.
Lucky Penny.
Okay.
The little ghost is helping me quite a bit.
Was that the stars?
Hey, we actually have a way now to get out from mom.
But not yet.
We're gonna remember that was there.
Okay, there we go.
Now we're gonna go in here.
Check it out.
We're gonna do this.
Batteries.
Oh, wait.
Oh, crap.
Placebo just became shit.
Oh, unless this fills it entirely.
It doesn't.
Hold on.
We need to use another pill that gives us a very small charge.
Open your mouth.
Okay.
Uh oh.
If there's nothing in the room, it's always worms.
That's the rule.
Damn.
Go, little haunt.
He's such a baller.
Look.
Thanks.
Come on, man.
What is that?
What do we have?
Question mark.
I'm actually gonna...
the magician.
Wait, how come that's revealed now?
Isn't that weird?
It wasn't revealed before what I mouse over did.
But now it is.
That doesn't make any sense.
Just because I bombed it, now I know what it is.
Huh?
Dude, what the hell?
Focus.
Good.
I want AWAS.
Oh, no, man.
Justice.
Okay.
I got a pill here.
We don't know what it is.
This is exciting.
You ready?
Yes!
Dude, we're gonna be spamming the shit out of that one.
It's gonna be really good.
I keep stepping on the stepping thingies.
Fuck me.
I'm so bad.
Give me money.
Give me... Oh, wait.
We have batteries in the other room.
At least some of them.
Ooh.
Hey, not bad.
Thanks.
Imagine a sun right now.
That'll go hard.
We can't do mom yet, though.
Not yet.
I've spotted some battery.
Wait, take the big one.
Yeah, that's it.
And now?
Good.
What was that one?
The stars?
That's the one I need.
Before I go to mom's.
No batteries here, unfortunately.
That is so sad.
He wants keys.
I actually like that.
Oh, wait.
I gave him the good one.
I didn't mean to.
Big, beautiful...
Why?
Why did that just remove all my tears?
Oh, okay.
Now it's back.
Now, to get to him, I'm gonna have to bomb, like, here.
Wonderful.
I need batter... I need the guy that gives me battery, man.
I need the mohawk, dude.
Imagine that.
I mean, that's... I mean, all the healing is good.
I can't give him my last.
That's pushing him.
You know what?
That eternal heart may actually be bad for me.
I don't wanna have fully red hearts, you know?
Gotta leave some room for the black hearts.
And blue hearts.
Shit.
Okay, fine.
Go in here.
That way, we're gonna get rid of the eternal.
Oh!
Removes curses.
Don't mind if I do.
Get rid of that curse.
I'm gonna keep my eternal.
Well, I guess I can just take damage on purpose.
Dude, I need more battery.
That's not enough.
Where could the secret be?
Maybe here.
Oh, I only have one bomb left.
Actually, it's looking quite promising that that's the spot.
Yeah.
Fucking hell, I'm so good.
Oh, what the... Get him, haunt.
Damn, man.
Okay, I guess I'll just have to go.
That is so sad.
It's fine, though.
Okay, get the stars.
I'm just confirmed that it does what I think it does.
Treasure room, got it.
Alright, here we go.
The long trek back to mom.
Wait, what was this one?
Oh, magician.
Oh, wait, it's not mom!
I've been boozled.
Fuck.
I thought it was mom.
Actually, I want this guy to damage me.
Take one damage.
I'm just gonna play.
I'm probably gonna take one damage.
There we go.
Eternal's gone, good.
Now we have a little room for the black hearts.
Uh,
ooh.
Not bad.
Well, obviously, I'm gonna go grab my pill now.
Or do I?
Do I?
Oh, no, wait, do I?
It's not guaranteed I get to keep or find another... Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Hold on.
We have one bomb left.
Shit.
Dude, I need one charge on my freaking thing.
We gotta be able to find that somewhere.
Let's really think about this.
Where could we find it?
Maybe in here.
Come on, please.
No!
There's nothing in here.
I can't believe it.
And really nothing in the shop?
Wait, spider mod!
Wait, when was this?
Since when has this been here?
No, I need bombs now!
You can't do me like this!
Okay, dude.
I'm going in.
I don't give a shit.
There's also this one.
Wait, that's also exciting.
Oh, that's really cool, man.
But it's gonna take a while to charge it.
Oh, shit.
Okay.
Let's see if we can find that last charge somewhere.
No, there's no way to do it now.
Actually, there is.
No, there's not.
There's no way to do it.
Give me this.
I think what I'm gonna do... I am going to take this.
I'm gonna take the pill.
I'm just gonna consume it because fuck it.
Whatever.
At this point.
Boom.
And now we get some mana.
But now we actually have a room free for a card.
Yeah, this one, of course.
The stars.
That's the one I need.
Okay, here we go.
It's gonna take a while to charge this, but it's gonna be crazy when we do, okay?
Go.
Ooh, now it's time for mom.
And there's no doubt.
I guess the way I can check it is just to look for this door.
If it's not there, then it's not mom, right?
Easy peasy.
That was a terrible room.
Oh my God.
Stop saying that.
I just lost my goddamn angel.
Doesn't matter.
I make my own luck.
I make my own angel items.
Wait a minute.
Fuck.
It's only soul and black hearts.
I thought it was battery.
I thought it was only soul and black hearts on Bethany when I had the item on Bethany because she's special with that.
Fuck.
I had no idea.
Well, it's pretty much useless to me now.
There's no way I'm fighting that many blue hearts.
I learned that the hard way.
You know what?
I'm gonna go step because I'm
angry.
Okay.
Blue heart.
That's the first.
I'll be back, maybe.
Stop earning.
Yeah, we're dead.
I may actually want this now.
I'm in big trouble.
I need some help.
Thank God I can get in there.
Is that it?
Mom?
Mom dead?
What happened?
She's dead.
I need more blue hearts.
I need the blue heart to fill me up.
Oh, not this room.
This room is so annoying.
Okay, at least we did it.
I kind of want to go back and step.
My tears are good.
Oh, that's nice.
More healing.
Fight club is unfortunately closed until further notice.
The world.
Love that.
I even have two bombs ready for this.
Let's make a little office here.
Step into it.
Man.
Yeah, you know what actually?
Now, I was about to say let's blow them up to get angel chance, but we need the last bomb for the other secret room.
Wait, where's the other secret room?
It's not here.
I'm so confused.
Why not?
What?
Oh, man.
Is that the black heart one, please?
Yes, I'm away.
It don't work like that.
I can't charge my thing with the other thing.
Oh, my God.
Unless, hold on, let me try and remember, does this actually spot the heart on the floor or on my thing?
No, we can't do this.
I need to take the virus.
I mean, or I take this and give up on the box, but I can't give up on carrot in the box.
I need to see what's in that box.
I take the virus.
You know what I should have done?
I should not have picked it up yet.
What if there's a backpack in here now?
Oh, thank God.
Okay.
Imagine if there was, man.
I would have screamed.
That's a bit too late for that one, but sure.
Okay.
Oh, load up.
Oh, yeah, that's fine.
Oh, man.
So that's the, that's the boss.
We got stars.
We are ready to rock and roll.
Isaac!
What
the hell is that?
Look at that.
We got a little key.
The Hank man as well.
Well, I'm not going to be able to use that, unfortunately.
Hold on a minute.
So the Hank man is going to be useless.
Didn't mean to blow that one up.
You take the... Ah, but wait a minute.
I can't do this because I got to get out of here as well.
So that's actually kind of ripped.
Unless I'm quick and I go, yep.
No.
Whatever.
Okay.
Now, now that we have that done, we move on.
And hopefully we get a bunch of blue hearts.
This is the plan.
And boogers.
No, with all the red hearts we have, I think it's a good idea to have the left hand.
Wait, actually, hold on.
It replaces all chests that spawn with red chests.
No, actually, I misunderstood that one.
Give me the booger.
There's also a card up here.
Don't go in there.
I almost went in there.
Oh my God.
That was close.
Okay, let's check what was in here.
Wasn't there something somewhere?
I don't know.
Let's find the exit.
I don't know, man.
This is looking a little interesting.
We need blue hearts.
Me doubt we're gonna find them.
But you gotta have hope.
The tower, better than nothing.
What is even happening?
Oh, it's the fire shooting me.
We need to destroy these.
No, I thought they would spawn blue hearts and stuff.
The creep on the floor is gonna be the enemy.
There we go, there we go, good.
Oh, I need bombs here.
That could have been it.
The hell?
That guy needs to calm down.
Dude, please.
Oh, that's mine, okay.
Oh, donate some HP, maybe.
I'm not sure.
Voodoo heads, spawn some more curse rooms, improve layouts and rewards.
I mean, I may as well do it at this point.
I have so much money.
Charge it up a little bit more.
The poke could go, actually.
Not too bad.
I'll take a card.
The moon!
That's the secret room.
I'm gonna buy a bomb as well, and this one.
I bought everything.
Sick.
Come on, we need blue hearts now.
Let me try and push it into the... let me see if I can do this right.
Okay, good, but unfortunately no blue hearts.
Solid.
I'm excited.
Very excited.
This is kind of an exciting run right now.
I would say it's all about the blue hearts and black hearts.
Lucky penny.
I'm gonna blow this up.
Yes!
Sick.
Whoa.
Friends, poison tears, flush or question mark?
I would say poison tears is pretty good, especially since I shoot so fast.
I like it.
I don't know what the question mark is, it could be bad, right?
Oh, I really need bombs here.
Let's find some more bombs.
Whoa.
Oh my god, what the fuck?
This is insane.
How do you avoid that?
Oh, maybe, oh, maybe pressing that button.
I probably would have done it.
It's not looking good, man.
I need bombs.
I need keys or bombs.
I've never seen this enemy.
There we go, that's what I needed.
Thank you.
I'm gonna gain access to a couple places now.
Oh, hello.
Okay,
so the places I needed to bomb was up here.
Yeah, this room, for example.
Dang it.
Nice.
We're almost there.
And then we had a room up here.
There we go.
Nice.
There we go, it's full.
You ready?
Uh...
Sacred Heart, holy water.
Sacred Heart is good.
That's a good one.
Also, oh, see, now the problem is, I can only have one blue heart.
Oh, I got no more keys.
Honestly, I like that.
I was too fast anyway.
Okay, good.
Now to find another active.
Oh god.
He acquired?
Yeah.
Wait, no, no, no.
This way.
And up here...
Open it.
There we go!
The fucking Bible!
We fly now!
Hell yeah.
That's huge.
The Bible active, though, is not gonna do much now.
What the fuck?
Didn't even see you there.
So that's the boss.
I'm not ready.
Now we're... I need some kind of active that heals my red hearts.
That would be ideal.
I've been in there already.
Uh... Do we want to change back?
Maybe.
I'll keep it.
The devil.
That's actually pretty good as well.
It may be better, actually.
Okay,
we're done here.
Time to move on.
Ah, give me the devil.
Up here...
And I'm out.
Okay, okay, looking good!
Looking real good.
Oh yeah, I can fly now.
I have to remember this.
There, this is... Ah man, flying is just so good.
One of the few joys.
Actually, one of the many joys.
A fat bat appears.
Oh, that's my poggy goat.
Hello!
What's that?
Bob's bladder?
Ooh, uh, no.
I'd rather keep my...
My, uh, what do you call it?
Boogers.
That feels better.
Hank, man, I don't need that.
I do need this, though.
Ha, my boogers attached to the inanimate objects.
Well, I guess technically these objects are animated, they're not inanimate.
But, you know what I mean.
I mean, everything's going according to plan here.
This is great.
Thank you.
Oh, dude, I want to do a speedrun today as well.
I want to fight Hoosh.
Wait, they're dead.
No, they're not dead, they're dead.
Okay.
Oh, wait,
I can fly.
Shit.
Wait, whoa!
Oh, wait, nevermind, no way.
Oh, I saw something.
I need spectral tears.
Don't make me so happy.
Not that hard.
Uh, wait, I have an eternal heart, I don't want that.
Uh, I don't want these anyway.
We gotta take some damage.
Hit me!
Don't kill him, don't kill him!
You idiot!
There we go, there we go.
We've done it, we've done it.
Shoot.
I should just run into them, actually.
That would be the way, you know.
Straight running into them.
He wants coins!
Oh, I gotcha.
I gotcha, buddy.
Dope.
Okay.
Sure.
We can do that.
That means you're gonna get even more.
No!
Not that!
48 hour energy could maybe be good, but...
Oh wait, let me do this.
See, the damage is good right now.
That thing died fast, and usually it's pretty tanky.
Also, I feel like I have homing tears.
I'm not sure where I got that.
Whoa!
I need to donate my money to something.
Imagine if I could find a shop and donate it all in the donation box, man.
That would be sick.
We're done here.
Don't let his light inside you.
It's the last thing you want to do.
More money.
Unidentified!
Ah...
Too bad.
I think we got this one in the back, guys.
This is looking very good.
Just another active would be the cherry on top right now.
A better active.
More money for some reason?
Don't need it.
I'm getting hit in every room.
Okay, grab the heart and move.
Go!
Ascension.
Basement two.
I actually kind of love this...
Saturnus thing I have.
It helps a lot.
Wait, why is he not dying?
Oh, he's my friend.
Wait!
Hold on.
Let me see my...
Yeah, give me that.
I'll take it.
It's not fantastic, but, you know, whatever.
I have very slow shot speed, man.
Fat, fat.
No.
That's fine.
I'm just gonna go.
Believe in me.
Wait, what, wait, wait, what?
I'm gonna try to use this somewhere special.
Oh my god.
Where could I use this?
Nothing here.
I'm taking a lot of damage right now.
Oh, right here.
That's it?
Come on.
There we go.
I think I'm just gonna...
Dude, I'm losing a lot of HP here.
I don't know if I should move on or stay.
I guess I should stay to heal up.
There we go.
Do I want this now?
Butt bombs.
You know what?
Why not?
Now's the time.
I feel it in my butt.
It's in there.
More healing.
Solid, more healing.
Now we're almost full HP.
As soon as I'm full HP, I'm moving on.
Wow, he died fast.
Oh, look at this place.
Oh, that's healing.
Very nice.
And we get to donate money here.
Also nice.
No, what the fuck was that?
Was that the butt bomb?
Bastards.
Can't believe it.
Need something really good.
No, not that.
You bastard.
Fine.
Here we go.
It's time.
We're home.
Only one though.
This is the problem, right?
You want to have a little more room there.
Hey, wake up.
Eden.
You unlocked challenge.
Nothing.
Okay.
Mom's purse.
Allows two trinkets to be held at the same time.
What am I going to get?
Dim bulb.
Grants an increase to all stats when held active items charges fully depleted.
That can easily be done.
For example, right now.
Boom.
That's a lot of extra stats.
We just got to remember to use it regularly so we have the stats.
Here we go.
Dogma.
Wait, are my tears being wasted on the fucking TV right now?
You saw that?
Three of them disappeared.
Easy, easy.
There we go.
Oh god.
Oh, the butt bombs.
I got to be careful of the butt bombs.
Dude, I'm also absorbing the red tears.
He's dead.
Okay, not bad.
Here we go, here we go, here we go.
Let's do this.
Oh, you bastard.
He got me with that one.
The good news is whenever my butt bombs happen, they fall to the floor.
So don't get hit by it.
It's actually very nice.
What the...
I just absorbed this shit, you saw that?
His mega attack, it's in my orbit.
Well, it was.
Now it's gone.
That is so funny.
Okay, he's dead.
Come on then.
Boom.
What the hell?
Okay, he's doing that stuff now.
I absorbed one of his projectiles.
One of the fiery ones.
I shouldn't have done that.
Speed down, no thanks.
Okay, he did.
It's a focus here.
Here come the buddies.
Wonderful.
Let's do this.
That's for you.
I hope you like boogers.
He's going to try and suck me in now.
Is he going to suck in my butt bombs?
Oh, crap.
Wow.
Oh, God.
That was bad.
Flappy birds.
Whoa, that was close.
But now?
Okay.
Damage is good.
Yo, how come I can't see my damage?
My stats are gone on the left.
What the hell is up with that?
Solid, solid.
Not bad at all, huh?
Let's see what we got.
I can't be stopped, man.
Eden.
Ever changing.
Okay.
I'm going to save that, guys, because right now there's one thing I want to do.
I want to play Azazel.
The modified one.
We're going for a speedrun on this guy.
I need a Azazel in my blood.
Let's go.
Good.
We don't have time for this.
Oh, cool.
I'll take that.
Shit.
That was very bad.
A credit card?
What was that one?
There's any purchasable items and pick up the...
Oh, that's crazy.
Still no treasure room, though.
Jesus Christ.
What the fuck was that?
You heard that?
Something was like...
And then I heard footsteps.
Dude, that actually fucking scared me just now.
What the fuck was that?
Hey!
A free PhD, baby!
Fuck yeah, dude.
Hold on, hold on.
Let me just...
I got a nice bad pill.
Nice pills.
Spawns a pill on pickup.
I mean, that's just straight up good.
There's nothing to say there.
PhD, baby.
That means we're pill-gaming now.
Wait, still no treasure room found.
I got to do that.
I know it's a speedrun, but still.
Also, I'm not flying.
Let's not forget.
Bump friend collects coin pickups and occasionally pays out with...
Yeah, I guess that's fine.
Interesting.
You know what?
Why not?
Nah, hold on.
Nah, nah, go, go, go.
Do it, do it, do it.
That's fine.
We're speedrunning.
This is how you go fast.
You skip rooms.
Cellar 2.
Uh, do I...
No, I'm gonna preserve my black hearts.
Yeah.
Oh, shit, I got to get in there.
Oh, no, we don't have time for this.
Ho, ho.
Wow.
Nice buffer.
Well, we already have buffer.
You know what I mean.
I just lost it.
Fuck!
You got to be kidding me.
I hate these animals.
Why did I go in here?
That was a waste of a key.
Guys, I'm playing so bad right now all of a sudden.
For no reason.
Good.
Go, go, go.
Uh, wait, we don't have to press those.
But I'm gonna do it.
Nice, I'm glad I did.
Log your foot.
Here we go.
Oh, god!
Man, is it over?
What the fuck?
He'd never done that before.
That's just bullshit, man.
That doesn't even count.
Like, I don't even know he could do that.
It's over for me.
That was that.
We had a good start, though.
That's just unbelievable.
I can't even go in there.
Oh, my goodness.
This is so bad.
Yeah, right.
No treasure room still.
We gotta go back.
Uh, beggar?
Come on, bomb.
Take him, take him, take him.
Faster!
Nothing?
Jesus.
I must have missed the treasure room in the beginning.
Six.
Why not?
Very, uh, underwhelming item, but, you know.
What can you do?
I got eight bombs.
Also, we don't have to hurry too much.
I mean, we just have to stay ahead of it, right?
And then we're... I'm gonna blow this guy up.
Okay.
Absolutely terrible second floor.
Nothing else to say there.
That was terrible.
We can't take any damage now.
Okay!
That's terrible.
Let's try again.
Bad start for sure.
I had to get used to the Azazel way of life, you know.
Got a pill.
Nice.
Go this way.
Mod up!
Oh my god, dude.
Are you actually serious?
Uh, yeah, why not?
Gimini?
Yeah, we need to tag him.
Tag him and bag him.
Wow!
Why did that hit me?
Oh my god, the tag is actually doing so much work.
Oh!
Dude, what is happening?
You hurt that, right?
Hold on, let's find the treasure room.
There's something going on, man.
Oh, yeah.
There it is.
Uh, mystery egg.
Following familiar that watches or hatches when Isaac takes damage.
Spawning a permanently charmed monster.
Strength of the monster is increased with each...
The egg regeneration.
Okay, sure, whatever.
Very underwhelming.
Again.
Dude, I'm gonna be crazy.
I'm gonna go in here.
I have a huge buffer, it's fine.
Fuck!
I'm so bad at the game!
Little horn is good.
I was gonna say, let's use the fool to get out.
But it's okay.
Let me actually just quickly see what's in here.
I have one coin, it's not gonna be enough.
One coin, I can blow this up, I don't wanna do it, we go.
Fuck it.
Move on.
We should still be in good time here.
Bro,
what is happening here?
I am just not playing well right now.
At all.
I'm too gung-ho with it.
Good.
Oh, I need that.
Ansys.
I have no words, honestly, dude.
I forgot that it's instant with the short range attack.
Destroying flames.
It's kinda nice.
Come on.
Show me the goods.
No!
What are you shit items?
I need a bomb.
What the fuck am I doing?!
Just fucking uninstall the game, dude.
It's over for me.
Yeah, I mean...
Insanity, just insanity.
I don't even know what's happening.
Why am I getting blue hearts?
I have 17 coins, I gotta go back.
There's no way I'm taking any deals, I can tell you that.
Okay, come on.
What the...
The fuck?
Pills, I like that.
Oh my goodness.
Hold on, we're on the timer.
Bombs a key.
Festus.
Lucky penny.
Another... Wow!
What the fuck?
Give me a key.
Alright, leave.
I'm happy with that.
Let's move.
We gotta go faster.
This was definitely too much time taken here.
Go.
We're going angel.
Angel.
Jesus.
Catacomb.
It is really worth it to hit them with the mark.
Jesus Christ.
What the...
I lost all my skills in the game in the last 10 minutes.
It's crazy, I'm gonna keep this.
They're just out of range.
Oh crap.
Oh my god!
Oh, my life flashed before me.
That was so scary.
Okay, okay, come on.
Angel.
I need you.
I'm gonna help.
I need to mark this guy.
No way!
He's marked.
Unbelievable.
I figured it out.
I know how to play this character now.
No, no angel, no!
We still haven't... What is it with this treasure room never being found before I find the boss?
Every single time.
Give me this, I need it.
We almost don't have time for a treasure room.
We gotta hurry.
Oh god.
Bombs galore, no keys.
Key acquired.
Treasure room.
Sure.
Oh, Jesus.
Okay, that's good.
We're leaving.
I think we are probably on the same time as the timer right now.
We're not ahead of it.
Next one needs to be faster.
Okay.
We are ahead of it.
Sick.
I thought it went terribly.
I mean it did, but you know, time wise.
Six, seven.
Pill?
Shit.
I'm gonna go get this card again.
Wait, what?
Oh no!
We had the shitty tear effect there.
I'm taking too much damage.
I need a satanic bible.
That is the only thing that will make me happy.
I can't get that.
Can't even pick that heart up.
Dude, that looks so cool.
Oh, please don't split me now.
Tears up?
Nice.
Oh no, wait.
Why?
My tears don't feel up.
What the frick is that?
Superball.
A chance to fire a bouncing tear.
Yeah, why not?
Better than what I have.
I don't even know how that would work with a laser, but okay.
Probably it doesn't.
Are we done?
Nope.
Okay, that's not bad.
Could be worse.
And having the close-up attack is making me play so risky.
I think that's why I keep taking damage so much.
I keep taking dumb risks.
Dude, I hate this randomized tear effect.
It's pissing me off.
Please die.
Oh my god.
I think this run is kaput, man.
I haven't just gotten any HP.
No red hearts yet.
That's usually the sign that the run is going to go downhill when you're playing a Saizel.
Try again.
This time, no stupid risks.
No more risky business.
We're going to play slow and calculated here.
Well, fast and slow, you know.
Otherwise it wouldn't be a speedrun.
Swift but cautious.
The hell is that?
Empty heart.
It multiplies?
I like the sound of that.
At the start of each floor, it grants one red health if the floor was entered with one red HP or less.
Aww.
You mean like, wait, one extra red health or just a healing?
Because the healing only sounds pretty bad.
I don't fuck with that at all.
Okay, this guy is going to explode, so let's not go crazy here.
No, it's not, okay.
What's happening there?
He's going to explode.
Kind of.
Nice.
I love when they just die from that first attack.
So satisfying.
I have to remember that my attack also pushes back projectiles.
That's kind of massive.
The lovers is useless for me.
I may as well take this.
Yeah.
Not too bad.
No HP lost.
I kind of want to mark this guy.
What the hell is that?
Does this guy gain new abilities every single time I fight him?
Dude, I'm so fucking tilted right now because of that.
You can't count on anything anymore.
It's insane.
Great.
Dakas.
Fool.
I'll take a Dakas.
I guess.
Tearspect.
Wait, wait, hold on, what?
Oh!
Yo, that's actually kind of good.
First time it's good.
Look at that.
That actually nullifies the bad thing.
Oh, I should really pause here.
It nullifies the bad part about the very narrow laser right now.
Okay, let's go.
Fuck it.
Speed run.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Aha!
Oh!
The floor was entered with one red HP or less.
So it doesn't give me more now.
That was it.
Fucking hell.
Good.
Oh, it's so much better now.
Piggy bank.
Why not?
Oh my god.
I can't, I can't.
I think this is the sign, guys.
I need to stop playing this now.
I'm clearly... I can't play anymore.
Like, this is too long of a session for me.
My brain is turning mush.
Uh, eight points.
I'll take this.
We need all the HP we can get.
Uh, please don't tell me the boss is in that room I skipped.
I'm gonna be so angry.
You're actually kidding.
Wow.
Go, go, go!
This guy's gonna be easy.
Boy, damn, he got blown the fuck up.
You know what?
Fuck it, we're going in here.
Dude, this is how, okay dude, this is how we're gonna do this.
I just figured it out.
If we keep taking devil deals, my thingy is gonna keep popping off.
Uh, what is this one anyway?
Death's touch.
More damage.
Yes, yes!
Absolutely, except we're pretty much dead now.
So yeah, that was kind of risky, guys.
Now we cannot get hit.
Fish me luck.
No, no, we're gonna get a red HP!
Right?
But it's not gonna be filled.
So we're still gonna be in danger until we heal.
Yeah.
I need to gamble a little bit here.
Come on, quick, we don't have time.
Speedrun.
Oh my god.
Wow.
That scared me.
Okay, let's go.
Holy shit.
Oh no.
I'm scared.
I gotta play fast, but also...
cautious here.
Where's my red hearts?
Ah, fuck off, man, will ya?
Aw, it's nothing this way.
Uh, no thanks.
I don't need that.
Ho, ho, ho, ho!
Wow, that's scary.
I can't even enter there.
Where's my healing?
Yeah.
Guys, I'm done.
I can't play anymore.
My brain is too mush for this.
Can't do it, man.
I think the three hour limit, that's when my capabilities just fall to zero.
That's my limit for this game right now.
Unless I am on two cups of coffee.
Maybe that's gonna do the trick.
But I will say, I'm usually very effective in the beginning.
And towards the very, very end.
Not today though.
Oh yeah.
There it is.
I am becoming tainted, yes.
That's a good way of putting it.
I'm the tainted man.
Next time we're gonna try the new tainted character we got.
This song is actually kind of a banger.
What's my tainted power?
Um, probably...
I don't know.
Making rotten potatoes in the microwave or something.
You know the, or poison potato from Minecraft.
Whatever it's called.
A shitty potato.
You shouldn't gamble on my success when it's been three hours.
Caffeine free for three hours, then drink two cups of coffee and stream for four more.
I don't think it works like that.
But I was thinking of doing a long stream at some point.
But not with Isaac, with something else.
Maybe switch it up between games.
You know, so when I start to lose in Isaac, we switch over to Sims or something.
Or something else completely.
Maybe we play My Little Pony Island or whatever else there is that is very relaxing.
Dude, all I wanted was to get to Hush.
And I was too eager, I was too...
You know what it is?
I think I was too...
Self-sure.
What is the word for it in English?
When you push ahead and you think you're more than you are.
What's the word for that?
Pride, yeah.
Pride is a good one, but it's not quite the word.
Yeah.
Overconfident, maybe?
Bullheart, yeah, something like that.
Hubris, that's it.
My hubris got the better of me towards the end.
I had so many great wins lately, I was like, I can't lose.
Especially not with the Azazel character.
But, you know...
I got put in my place.
Tainted Azazel is a high-risk character, it's natural to make mistakes.
Yeah, actually it is.
It's not like the normal Azazel, that one is a lot more forgiving.
One, because you can fly, and two, because you can have...
What's the word for that?
You can fly...
and...
What's the other thing?
Yeah, I guess it's just flying.
Flying is just so big.
I can literally just sit inside of a rock and shoot.
That's the safety that normal Azazel provides, right?
Oh, spectral tears, that's what I wanted to say.
But I guess I already have spectral tears on the tainted version.
I just can't sit in the rocks, that's it, yeah.
Tainted...
Lilith also has a melee attack, yeah.
Wait, what?
But he has pretty good range, so it's not...
I don't even remember what tainted Lilith is.
Oh, right!
The fetus character.
Yeah, yeah, right.
I mean, yeah, you could call it a melee.
I would call it a melee range, in a weird way.
Just the extra range is so nice.
Also, I forgot how tiny the range is on the close attack.
On tainted Azazel.
I seem to remember it being longer.
But you actually, you gotta be, like, kissing them, pretty much.
Did Oliver go Pride Day challenge?
What are you talking about?
What is that?
You should do that, if not for Pride Month?
I don't understand what you're talking about.
What is a Pride Day challenge?
It's just one of the challenge...
Oh, okay, okay, I see.
I thought you meant something else.
One of the challenges is Pride Day.
Got it.
I see.
In-game.
I thought you meant, like, oh, has Oliver tried going gay?
You know, like, did he do the gay challenge?
I don't know what you guys meant by that, but now I see.
It makes sense.
That felt so out of the blue, you know?
Maybe that should be the title of the video when I finally do the Pride challenge.
Gay challenge.
Yeah, I actually wanted to do challenges today, Nemo, but I...
I had so much fun with just the normal runs and stuff.
I'll get to it at some point.
Maybe I'll have, like, an only challenge day or something.
My brain is just turning too mush.
Three hours is the limit for me on this game, I think.
Otherwise, it's gonna be a bad spiral where I just keep losing and I get tilted and then...
eventually I'll win, but it's gonna take a while.
Exactly.
Will you give Samson another chance?
Maybe.
Maybe I will.
Maybe I won't.
I think it would be a lot more fun if I didn't have Ludo.
Let's just say that.
I think Ludo kind of ruined that for me.
You tried to get to hush, kept trying to rush, brain turned to mush, win streak went flush.
Bars.
What's your favorite and least favorite tainted character?
Least favorite is obviously Samson.
Dude, I almost want to say Eulith.
But I only had one run with her, but man, that felt good.
That felt strong.
But it's gotta be a sizzle, I think.
Even though it didn't go too well right now, I still had so much fun playing him.
Yeah, the fetus whip is crazy.
Speaking of fetuses and stuff...
Have you guys seen the show...
The Nick?
I saw the first episode, and boy, that was...
Phew!
Man, I had trouble watching the screen.
It was so disgusting.
Reminded me a little bit of that.
It's so good.
I heard it's so good.
I'm usually not into those period dramas.
But everyone was praising it so much, so I gave it a chance.
And I will say the first episode was banger.
So I'm actually looking forward to seeing more of it.
Being Danish, I'd imagine he's better with his hands.
I don't know what that means.
What does that have to do with being Danish?
I can't confirm or deny.
There's actually a double meeting there, Don.
You're right, with the period drama.
But that's not what I meant.
Scroll more?
I don't know.
What am I looking for?
I have no idea what you're talking about.
Am I a good kisser or not?
I don't know.
How would I know?
Have you ever played this game called Minesweeper?
Oh, actually, I was planning on doing a blind playthrough of it.
Yeah.
People have been saying it's good for a long time now.
I think I'm gonna play it.
24-hour... Dude, 24-hour Minesweeper stream would fry me.
I actually think I may die physically.
I will collapse.
My lungs will give out.
My hands will become sweaty.
There may or may not be spaghetti.
But it's gonna be bad.
Guys, I gotta admit something.
I don't know how Minesweeper works.
When I was a kid, I would just click on squares.
And hope I won.
I had no idea how to play that game.
I still have no idea how it works.
I'm assuming you need to calculate some shit because there's numbers.
But, man, I don't know.
Is that just the whole game?
There's gotta be, like, some calculation involved.
Right?
You still do that?
Right.
It shows number and it means how many bombs around this number.
Huh.
Oh, I see.
So if you have one area with, like, a number four and another area with a number...
One.
Yeah, then you know that in that area that would be one and...
But the one could also be part of the four in the other area if they were overlapping, I guess.
Ah, it's gonna get complicated.
Just saying, Danish people are known for crafting with their hands.
Whittling little wooden horses and baking intricate pastries and the likes.
Well, not me.
I am not good with my hands, okay?
I can't, for the life of me, wield a saw.
Or a hammer or whatever.
I will say, I did put up my, uh...
What do you call those...
Sound absorbing panels.
And I had to use, like, a special saw.
To cut out a little piece so it would fit around the electrical outlet on the wall.
That took so much time for me.
Even just hanging pictures on the wall, dude, I'm doing, like, a million calculations that is probably over-killing it.
When I could just do something more simple, I don't know.
I overthink things so much, it takes me a whole day.
I'm not good at it.
Guys, I'm not gonna remember the stuff for Minesweeper.
I care so little about Minesweeper, it's crazy.
Just seeing you guys talk about Minesweeper actually depresses me.
I get more sad.
Because I don't like it.
I hate that game.
I'm sorry.
Maybe I will love it if I understand it.
That's probably why I don't like it, because I don't understand it.
Mad because bad, probably.
I will say, you're probably right.
Ah, Kimo could Dragon, that's okay, we're ending now.
This is not the beginning.
So you can catch the VOD.
I'm gonna upload it ASAP.
I may also play some Red Dead tonight.
I didn't play any Red Dead the last couple of days either.
I was in my no-gaming mood.
You sound like someone that keeps finding Mines.
Yeah.
I definitely do.
I'm not good at avoiding those.
I don't know when next stream is, guys.
Maybe tomorrow, maybe the day after.
I will say almost 100% chance that it's within two days.
I think I will play Red Dead 2 after the first one.
Yes, I'm looking forward to it quite a bit.
The first game is banger, man.
It is so good.
I'm mostly excited to see where they're gonna innovate, you know?
Like, how they're gonna take this formula further.
So that's what I'm looking forward to.
But also, of course, just the story of it.
Thanks for the RDR videos.
Favorite LP in a while, and it made me replay the second game.
Okay.
You played the first one, though, right?
I mean, I don't know about the second, but the first one slaps already.
I can't wait for the second.
I know that people like the second more than the first.
Like, it's very highly acclaimed.
The Red Dead 2 is one of the highest rated games of all time.
I cried like a bitch.
That's good.
It means you have empathy, and you enjoy good stories.
I would recommend trying Undead Nightmare at least once.
Oh yeah, I wanted to do that, actually.
I'm gonna try it.
I would say there's maybe a 5% chance I won't try it.
Super Land?
What is that?
Have I added that to my list?
Let me see here.
Oh yeah, it is on my list already.
It's in my backlog.
Here, you can see the backlog on this link.
Play it, okay?
Play it?
I'm gonna play all the games.
Dude, guys, I will almost certainly outlive my backlog.
If you think about all the great games that spawn every year, and how many I actually complete, mathematically it's not looking good.
You know, unless I start to hustle.
I will die not having played all the games.
I need a clone.
Dude, I actually had a dream about cloning myself.
To play games.
But it was spawned because the day before I had this idea, so I was making pancakes.
Right?
And I'm standing near the stove.
And I have this pan, and I'm making the pancakes.
And it's so slow.
You know, I pour it in and it takes forever to make a pancake.
So I thought, dude, why don't I just clone this pan?
And use two of the stove tops.
And then alternate between them to create twice as many pancakes.
I didn't do it, but I could.
And then I guess I dreamt about cloning myself to gain more.
That is stupid.
But yeah.
Some YouTubers have an AI version that does videos for them.
What?
How is that enjoyable at all?
I mean, I get AI is good nowadays, but it's not that good.
Maybe that's just me.
That sounds terrible.
I mean, who knows, maybe in the future it'll be great, but right now that shit is bad.
I wouldn't watch that.
The fact that we will all have to dream this eventually.
What if this is a dream, man?
Maybe I should make a secondary YouTube channel where I just post random slop and start earning money on that.
Like the ultimate slop channel.
It basically just crawls the internet, copies scripts word for word.
And just uploads it, you know?
Boom.
Money.
I don't actually think that's allowed.
I think you will actually have your channel closed nowadays, if you do that.
Yeah, exactly, Nemo.
I heard that too.
They're cracking down on that shit.
Get banned challenge.
Something like that.
I also think, I've heard this, I'm not sure if it's true.
But if you do that shit, and YouTube knows that you're the same person with another channel, like the one I have right now.
It will actually close down my channel as well, like the main channel I have.
So there's absolutely no reason for me to do this.
This is such a bad idea.
Don't do it.
It's gonna fuck you over.
It's called inshittification also.
And not just slopification, it's everywhere.
Did you watch the Swedish PSA about inshittification, or was it Norwegian?
I forgot.
But it's quite funny on YouTube.
Just search for inshittificator or something.
You've seen that?
I mean, that's exactly how it is.
Netflix is a great example of that.
Netflix was so good when it first came out, man, that even I got a Netflix subscription, and I almost never paid for stuff like that.
It was so convenient, it had great shows on it.
The catalog was amazing, it was so convene- the way it worked just worked.
And now it's just shit.
Now I don't want to pay for that anymore.
They got more expensive, there's ads everywhere.
They don't even have the things I want to watch half the time.
Terrible.
I don't want to juggle ten different subscriptions, you know, to different things.
But yeah.
So you start by making it good, get all the people in, and then you make it shit.
Maximize profits, disregard people's enjoyment.
I dread the day Steam falls to that, man.
When Gaben leaves this Earth, I also dread what's gonna happen.
I feel like it's gonna go downhill as soon as he's gone.
Steam is a great place.
But I mean, it's not all- it's not like all, you know, sunshine either.
The guy is, you know, profiting off of pretty much just gambling.
That's what Dota and Counter-Strike is nowadays, right?
But whatever.
It is what it is.
All in all, I would say praise Gaben for sure.
Gaben is cool.
He's gotta make his bag.
I'm rebranding as an AI startup, please give me billion dollars.
That's how it works, man.
I would love a channel dedicated to Jackie.
What would be on the channel, though?
Like, what kind of videos would you want to watch?
Here's a video of Jackie sleeping.
Here's Jackie jumping or... I don't know, meowing or something.
I mean, okay.
I can put some videos on the More Oliver channel.
I'm not gonna make a whole channel for it, that's maybe too much.
But yeah, we can definitely, like, I have a decent camera now.
I can probably make some cool videos of Jackie.
Yeah, let's do that.
That Jackie cam is not that cool, though, because she moves around all the time.
It's not as fun as it sounds.
Definitely better to have, like, an edited video where I get some cool clips of her.
I would be so sad if my More Oliver channel started getting more subscribers because of Jackie.
That, I mean, okay, maybe not sad, but I would just be surprised.
Jackie's just taking over.
A sleeping stream, no.
With Jackie, I mean, she's just sitting there.
Speak enough.
It's almost time to feed her.
I'm gonna go, guys.
Thank you so much for watching.
We made some good progress today.
Unlog even more char- I feel like I'm unlocking characters every single day now.
I'm just kind of killing it.
I gotta say it.
I am.
Nice.
See you next time.
Bye-bye.